The Interhigh singles preliminaries are approaching!
（卓(たく)）いよいよ
個人戦の予選会も近いが—
I want you to go in there ready to take all four slots again this year!
今年も本戦出場４人すべて
うちが占める覚悟でいく！
Yes, sir!
But our block is packed with tough guys like Kong of Tsujidou and Tsukimoto of Katase,
ただし予選とはいえ
辻堂(つじどう)のコン 片瀬(かたせ)の月本(つきもと)ら—
本戦を上回る
猛者(もさ)の多いブロックだ
who are even better than the
guys we'll face at the Interhigh!
Don't let your guard down! Got it?!
絶対 気を抜くなよ！ いいな！
Yes, sir!
（部員たち）押忍！
Wow, they're already serving cold noodles!
（ペコ）うほー！
もう冷やし中華 出てるんすね
I never get tired of eating here. So many seasonal options!
季節感あるメニューも豊富で
飽きないっすよ
（国分(こくぶ)）そりゃいいけどよ ペコ
That's nice, Peco,
but how will you pass high school if you're always here?
お前 ずーっと うちにいっけど
高校 平気なんか？
It's no problem.
ノープロブレムっす
単位 計算して
バックレ決めてますから
I've calculated how often I can skip and still graduate.
You go to Katase, right?
お前 片瀬だよな
Yeah.
（ペコ）はい
There's a chopper there named Tsukimoto.
（国分）
月本ってカットマン
いんべ？
Uh, yeah.
強(つえ)えの？
Is he good?
50連勝とかっつう話さ
They say he's on a fifty-game winning streak.
なあ？ ペコ
Is it true, Peco?
Yeah, it is.
はぁ そうっすね
Well, my kid brother's on a high school team, and he played Tsukimoto once.
（国分）いや うちの弟も
高校で打ってんだけどよ
いっぺん対戦したらしいんだ
Said he's out of this world.
もう 全然すげえって
人間業じゃねえって話よ
Like, superhuman!
Apparently he's so tough he made my brother wonder if he should quit.
卓球 続けてく自信なくすほど
強(つえ)えってな
Oh?
ふーん
（国分）ロボットと
打ってるみてえなんだと
He said it was like playing a robot.
What? This is the old lady?
え？ これオババ？
マジ かわいいじゃん
She was a real cutie.
Hey, no giving Peco beer!
（道夫(みちお)）
ペコにビールはダメだぞ
I know we've got juice and stuff!
ジュースあったろう ジュース
お前 初めて来た時
母ちゃんの銅像 写真撮ってたろ？
Didn't you take a pic of Mom's bronze statue when you first got here?
（カメラのシャッター音）
（ペコ）ピンポンガール！
Ping Pong Girl!
あちゃ…
Yikes.
This is Mr. Koizumi.
これが小泉(こいずみ)さんで…
Huh?
これが海王(かいおう)理事長
風間(かざま)のじいさんだ
And this is the chairman of Kaiou, Kazama's granddad.
（赤ん坊の泣き声）
（ペコ）ホントだ
Wow, so it is!
There, there.
Up you go!
ほらあ！
It's a small world, huh?
狭いね 世の中
They were all childhood friends.
みんな 幼なじみさ
Now eat something and go to sleep!
飯食って早く寝ろ
Oh, and Mom's worried about your knee.
それから
母ちゃん お前の膝 心配してたぞ
A knee injury's what made her quit table tennis, after all.
母ちゃんも卓球やめたの
膝いったからだからなあ
You sure you're okay?
大丈夫なんだろうな？
（ペコ）ほーい
Yup.
Don't sleep here.
（道夫）ここで寝んなよ
（百合枝(ゆりえ)）
いつも風呂に入ってるのね
You're always in the bath.
I hear Poseidon's providing mats for the Interhigh preliminaries.
インターハイ予選—
ポセイドンがマットを敷くって
決まったみたい
They're doing it to promote sales.
発売促進のためだって
And all the Kaiou players will be wearing special mat shoes called "Dragon."
そして海王の選手は—
“ドラゴン”っていう
マット専用のシューズを—
みんなで履いてるの
竜(りゅう)ちゃんは
自分のために卓球をするべき
You should play table tennis for yourself, Ryuu.
I'm getting out of here!
私は ここから出るよ
Don't make that scary face.
怖い顔しないで
Huh, I didn't know Hoshino still played table tennis.
（小泉）そうか
星野(ほしの)は まだ卓球続けてたか
And since you didn't do your job with him, I had to work my butt off.
（オババ）お前さんが手を抜いた分
こっちが えれえ苦労したよ
禁煙だから ここ
You can't smoke in here.
All right. I'll register him too, then.
分かった
そういうことなら
彼も登録しておくよ
不思議とチームの信望 厚い子だ
He's strangely popular with the team.
They probably won't mind—they'll welcome him, even.
歓迎こそされ 反感はないだろう
Question for you, Ms. Tamura.
ミズ田村(たむら)に１つクエスチョン
What are the odds of this bowl-headed Hoshino of yours beating Tsukimoto at the next Interhigh?
その おかっぱ頭の星野がね—
次のインハイで
月本に勝つ確率ってさ—
どれっくらいあるの？
ちっ てめえが
見捨てた選手じゃねえかよ
You're the one who wrote him off.
That's not an answer.
（小泉）答えになってないよ
I'm not good at predicting odds.
確率うんぬんは苦手だね
You can't compare that kid to other people,
あの子は 他と
比べられないんだよ
so it's hard to tell.
だから見極めにくい
But if we're talking about talent alone,
he's far better than Kaiou's Kazama Ryuuichi.
しかし才能だけで言うなら—
海王の風間竜一(りゅういち)を
はるかにしのぐ
I can say that much for sure.
そいつだけは確かだ
No way.
ウッソ～
I will become stronger!
（ドラゴンの声）私は強くなる
父より！ おじじより！
Better than my farther!
Better than my grandfather!
（ドラゴン）ぬおおー！
A new age has dawned, and still I can't make a decision
My path is too straight for my taste, but I'll walk it
I can't choose just yet
I have to think about it
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm going crazy!
Comparing yourself to others just makes you depressed
You're alone in this world
You're always alone here
Still you're gonna do it, right?
Maybe there's nothing that only I can do
But there's no way that I
But there's no way that I won't try to leave my mark
I just want to have my fun, whatever the times
Interhigh Preliminaries
Kanagawa Tournament
おい あれ月本 誠(まこと)じゃねえか？
Hey, isn't that Tsukimoto Makoto?
He's right. It's Tsukimoto of Katase High.
ホントだ　片高(かたこう)の月本だよ
What is he doing?
何してるんだ？
誰か待ってんのかね
Waiting for someone, maybe?
That was Tsukimoto, from Katase High.
（学生）今の月本だぜ 片高のよ
Really? That's him?
（学生）へえ あれか
Hey, Tsukimoto!
（大田(おおた)）おーい 月本！
Get in here!
そろそろ中 入れ
The vibe's kinda different from before!
何だか 様子が違うぞ
Here they are. So hardcore!
来た 来た　すげえな
Look at those heads.
何ちゅう頭じゃ
You think they'll take the top four spots again this year?
（学生）
しかし今年も やっぱし あれかね
上位４人は全員 彼らで決まりかね
I don't know about this year.
（学生）
いや 今年は分かんねえよ
For one thing, there's Tsukimoto from Katase High, right?
ほれ あいつ
片高の月本 いるしよ
Rumor has it that Dragon inputted
Tsukimoto's data into his practice robots.
ドラゴンは卓球ロボットに—
月本のデータ インプットして
練習してたって うわさだぜ
（浜(はま)ちょん）うへえ マット！
Mats!
（高村(たかむら)）床にマット敷いてあっぞ
They've got mats on the floor!
I dunno, I guess maybe it is kinda slippery?
分っかんねえなあ
滑るって言われりゃ滑る気も…
Are you serious?
（高村）どんだけ どんだけぇ
（木村(きむら)）イテ！ 滑った
Ow! I slipped.
（小枝）マジかよ バカ
Seriously? You're always falling down, moron!
お前 いつも転んでんだろ バカ
Kazama said the special mat shoes felt "completely different," remember?
風間が マット専用シューズは
全然 違うって言ってたろ？
That was a TV commercial, moron.
バカ ありゃＣＭだろ？ バカ
They were on sale outside, right?
表で売ってたよな
Size 27.5, please!
World's
First!
Mat Shoes
（選手）7.5 下さい！
Here you are!
（店員）はい 毎度
Size 26.5.
（選手）26.5
（店員）はい どうぞ
There you go!
世界のグラウンドはマットだ
International arenas have mats!
全然 違う
It's completely different.
Leap out into the world!
世界へ飛び出せ！
The world's first shoes made especially for mats!
世界初！ マット専用シューズ
Gimme, gimme!
（選手）ちょうだい ちょうだい
（選手）28ある？
Have any 28s?
（選手）26.5！
（選手）急いで！
Size 26.5!
I checked out the tournament brackets!
（道夫）
トーナメント表 見てきたよ！
Thanks.
（オババ）ご苦労さん
（道夫）
マットは 多分 関係ないよ
I doubt the mats make a difference!
No pro athletes change their shoes based on mats vs. bare floor!
マットと床で
シューズを替えるプロ選手はいない
They're just trying to whip up sales!
販売目的で あおってんだ！
So how did it look?
（オババ）それで どうだった？
Where's Smile?
スマイル どこ？
小泉と競技場だけどね
In the stadium with Koizumi.
Jeez! I wanted to say hi!
何だよ
ひと声かけてやりたかったぜ
Hey!
（オババ）おい
（道夫）ん？
The bracket.
（オババ）トーナメント表
Well, the first round is a first-year I know who'll be easy to beat, but...
うーん １回戦は知ってる１年坊で
楽勝なんだけど…
はっきり言いな
Just spit it out.
おい ペコ！
お前の２回戦の相手
Hey, Peco!
I saw your second round opponent!
誰？
Who is it?
It's Kong Wenge!
（道夫）コン・ウェンガだ！
What's wrong, Wenge?
Homesick?
Something like that.
そっか　２回戦で
もうチャイナね
Really? I've got China in the very second round?
But if you make it past that, it's a cakewalk until the semifinal against Kazama!
だが それ越えたら—
また準決勝の風間まで
大した相手はいない
What about Smile?
スマイルは？
If you play Smile, it'll be in the final.
スマイルと当たるとすれば
決勝だ
There's no one in his way except
maybe Sanada in the third round.
やつの邪魔といえば
３回戦で当たる真田(さなだ)ぐらいで—
あとは敵じゃねえな
The others don't stand a chance.
（ペコ）強いの？ そいつ
Is Sanada good?
He's Kaiou's vice captain.
海王の副将だ
Oh.
そう
サンキュー 道夫さん
おいら 行く
Thanks, Michio.
I'm off.
What's up? There's plenty of time before your match!
何だ　試合まで時間あるぞ
I'm gonna go.
行っとくよ
そうか
よーし ぶちかましてこい！
Really?
Okay! Show 'em who's boss, then!
Make a big name for yourself, Peco!
どーんと男を上げてこいよ ペコ！
I figured that'd get him down, but he's taking it in stride, huh, Mom?
ちったあ
気落ちするかと思ったが—
案外 けろっとしてやがるな
母ちゃん
When you're aiming for the top, you're bound to face monsters eventually.
（オババ）てっぺん目指せば
いずれは怪物にぶつかる
I guess he'd steeled himself for this.
腹くくったってことだろうよ
Oh man, this blows.
あっちゃー 最低 最悪
Seriously?
マジかよ　死にてえ
Just kill me now...
You might not believe this,
but my team is getting pretty good.
It was like teaching babies to read and write.
Today's singles matches may be rough,
but they'll go far in the team events.
I look forward to it.
It's true.
I trust you, Wenge.
Is the strongest one still that Kazama Ryuuichi?
Yeah.
But this year, there's a player who's a threat to him.
Do you remember him, Coach?
Tsukimoto Makoto.
Oh, the kid with the glasses...
It's sure to be a good fight.
I won't play them until the semifinals.
First, I'll make it into the top four and head to nationals.
I look forward to it.
Just once, I'd like to beat Kazama and earn my ticket home.
Sounds good. I'm sure you can do it.
Not gonna wear the mat shoes?
（真田）
マットのシューズは履かんとね？
ああ 私にシューズは関係ない
No. Shoes make no difference to me.
風間が履かんで
俺らだけ履いとったら—
Sure looks dumb if we all wear them and Kazama doesn't.
カッコ悪かばいね
I've worn Butterfly shoes since I was in China.
私は中国にいる時から
バタフライを履いている
I wear the same ones on mats and bare floors.
マットもフローリングも
靴は替えないよ
Wait, really?
（部員）え！ ホント？
We bought them!
買っちゃった
But wearing good shoes is good.
でも いい靴を履くのはいいこと
Everyone should wear good shoes.
みんな いい靴 履くべき
Ball Select Station
Hey, Kong and Dragon aren't wearing mat shoes.
（男性）おい コンやドラゴンは
マットシューズ履いてないぜ
（男性）風間が？
Kazama isn't?
The mats don't bother you?
マットは気にならんのかね？
No, they don't.
（スマイル）はい 気になりません
Anyway, don't you have any strategic advice, Coach?
それより 戦術的なアドバイスとか
ないのですか？ 先生
None at all.
ないよ そんなもん
私の知るかぎり—
You're already the greatest player in my eyes, Mr. Tsukimoto.
君は最高のプレーヤーだよ
ミスター月本
I know you will win.
君の勝利を私は確信している
（男性）
コン！ ぶちかましてくれ！
Destroy him, Kong!
（男性）海王けずれー！
Get Kaiou!
Go, Kaiou!
（男性）いけー 海王！
（男性）コン 吹っ飛ばせ！
Blow Kong away!
It's time to dance.
Yes!
Damn. They're just drives!
（毛利の声）
クソッ んだがドライブ！
ちっ ダメでねえか こりゃ
I got no hope.
I'm just no match for him.
まったく歯さ立たねえ
こいが世界レベルが
This is what world-level play is like, huh?
I finally made first string at Kaiou,
やっと 海王の
レギュラーさ なれだのに—
デビュー戦が こいが
and this is how my first match goes?
ハァ…
Is it talent?
才能が…
Will I get yelled at?
怒られっかな
Nah, maybe I only ever made first string because Kaiou ain't what it was.
いや
んだども わぁが
レギュラーさ なれたのも—
海王が落ぢぶれてきたせいかも
しれねえからな
はなっから
誰も わぁさな期待してねっか
Guess nobody expects much from me.
Eleven-two!
（主審）イレブンツー
マッチ トゥ コン選手
Match goes to Kong!
（毛利）無残…
Pitiful.
Tsujidou Academy
Second-Year
Kong
Wenge
Katase High
Second-Year
Hoshino
Yutaka
Katase High
Second-Year
Tsukimoto
Makoto
Kaiou Academy Second-Year
Nekota
Shuuji
Advance to the Second Round
Kaiou Academy Second-Year
Sanada
Masayuki
First Seed
First Round Bye
Kaiou Academy
Third-Year
Kazama
Ryuuichi
First Seed
First Round Bye
I did it! I won!
やったー！ 勝ったよ！
Thank you, Kong.
ありがと コンさん
That was just the first round.
まだ１回戦よ
But I was up against Higashi from South High!
だって 相手は南(みなみ)高の東(ひがし)だぜ
バーカ 俺だって
キタ高のやつ 倒したんだぜ
So what, moron? Even I beat a guy from North High.
Listen up. Practice hard and you will get stronger.
いいか　ちゃんと練習すれば
みんな強くなる
That's truth.
これ ホントよ
Then if I work myself to death,
will I be able to play like Tsukimoto?!
じゃあ
俺も死ぬほど頑張ったら—
片瀬の月本みたいになれる？
（チャイナ）それ ない
（部員たち）アハハハ
Not a chance.
ウソ　分からないね
Joking. Who knows?
才能 どこか眠ってるかもよ
Maybe talent is sleeping somewhere inside you.
Call me when you're in a pinch!
Chant this three times in your mind!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
If you do that,
I'll
come to you
Enter the Hero
The second round matches will now begin.
（アナウンス）
ただいまより第２回戦を行います
各選手は指定された台に
ついてください
Players, please report to your designated tables.
ハハッ 私 あなた覚えているよ
I remember you.
ヘヘッ
忘れてくれりゃあ よかったのによ
I wish you'd forgotten.
どっこい俺様
１年前とは ちと違う
FYI, I'm a little different from last year.
Japanese penhold with a rubber on the back! This guy...
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
ヘヘッ
リニューアルされてんからよ
I've been remodeled.
Keep that in mind, Kong!
そこんとこ よろしくだぜ コン
Game goes to Tsukimoto!
（主審）ゲーム トゥ 月本選手
Tsukimoto Makoto is nothing if not brilliant.
（卓）見事と言うほかないな
月本 誠
Perfectly efficient movements,
stroke variations, control, and speed.
ムダのない動き　配球
コントロール　スピード
He's phenomenal at everything.
すべてが桁違いだ
Ryuuichi.
（卓）竜一
（ドラゴン）ああ… 押忍
Yes, sir.
どうした
What's wrong?
12番台
Table twelve.
コン・ウェンガ
Kong Wenge.
はい
Yes, sir.
Watch closely.
よく見ておけ
間違いなく上で当たる
You'll definitely go against him later.
それは どうでしょう
I'm not so sure about that.
（卓）ん？
（ドラゴン）彼—
He's going to lose the first game.
ファースト 落としますね
アウト！
Out!
テンセブン　星野選手
Ten-seven, Hoshino!
Crap!
Wenge...
Hoshino? Who is that?
星野？ 誰だよ
I don't know.
（ドラゴン）
分かりません
Kong's probably panicking right about now.
今頃 コンの頭の中は
パニックだろうぜ
何せ １年前にスコンクで
吹っ飛ばした相手なんだからね
This is someone he skunked a year ago, after all.
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
Is this really the same guy from last year?
He's completely different.
That guy didn't have drives. Is he someone else?
He's fast!
Ugh!
No! It's him!
He hasn't overcome his weak backhand side.
Why no RPB shots, then?
Isn't that what the rubber is for?
Does he not have a reverse side?
Does it not exist?
He doesn't really have a backhand, Wenge!
Don't let the racket fool you!
He hasn't mastered the RPB style yet!
That's it!
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
ニーハオ！
Ni hao.
This kid... That's it!
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
Right there.
（オババ）そこだ
（コーチ）あ…
Damn!
Eleven-eight!
（主審）イレブンエイト
Game goes to Hoshino!
ゲーム トゥ 星野選手
Kong lost a game.
（男性）コンがゲーム取られたぜ
That penholder's using both sides of the bat!
（男性）あのペンホルダー
裏 使ってんぞ
Go over all the data on Hoshino of Katase again.
（猫田(ねこた)）
片高 星野　データ洗い直せよ
His backhand was almost like a forehand.
（男性）
フォアみてえなバックでしたね
（道夫）あの野郎
That punk...
I told him to test his reverse side against weaker opponents first.
裏面は まず格下で試せったのに
（オババ）ふん
The better your opponent, the more effective bluffs are.
ハッタリなんてのは
相手が一流であるほど きくんだよ
Love ya, Peco.
愛してるぜ ペコ
Oh yeah!
シャラーッ！
ちょっと 君
You there!
You're in the middle of a game, Tsukimoto!
試合中だよ 月本選手
Right.
（スマイル）はい
I'm sorry.
すみません
Welcome back, hero.
おかえり ヒーロー
おや
Oh?
あらら
My, my.
He just up and learned the Chiquita and its reverse!
（道夫）チキータもミュータも
急に覚えやがった
What an unbelievable kid.
（オババ）まったく なんて子だよ
He grows right before your eyes.
みるみる間に成長してく
Yeah.
It's probably a game to him.
あの子にとっちゃ
遊びなんだろうよ
The way he kicks people in the back to
instantly climb up the ranks is terrifying.
人の背中ん蹴って
あっという間に駆け上る
恐ろしいほどだ まったく
The reasonable assumption is probably that Kong panicked and went off his game.
コンが焦って自滅したとみるのが
妥当だろうな
Yes.
しかし…
However...
（ペコ）っしゃー！
（チャイナ）う…
Yeah!
Nine-six, Hoshino!
ナインシックス　星野選手
ハハッ
覚えてるか？ あなた
Do you remember?
The first time you play me,
you can't take one point off me.
私と初めて試合した あなた—
１点 取れない 私から
Xie xie, Kong.
（ペコ）
シェーシェーだぜ
コンさん
It's all thanks to you that I managed to get better.
あんたのおかげで—
おいら １つ
強くなることができたよ
You taught me how to fly!
あんたは
おいらに飛び方を教えてくれた
（ドラゴンの声）才能か
Talent, huh?
Done already, Mr. Tsukimoto?
もう済んだのかね
ミスター月本
Yes.
（スマイル）ええ
（小泉）さすがに早いな
That was quick.
（スマイル）
見てくださらなかったんですか？
You didn't watch me?
No. I knew you'd win anyway.
（小泉）ノー どうせ勝つ試合だ
（スマイル）負けましたよ
（小泉）え？
I lost.
What?
Just kidding.
（スマイル）冗談ですよ
星野ですね
Hoshino, huh?
Yeah. He's playing an interesting game.
ああ 彼 面白い卓球を
やっているよ
He's an RPB... driver...
裏面… ドライブだ
What? You're not going to watch?
何だ 見ていかないのか？
I know he'll win anyway.
どうせ勝つ試合です
Out!
（主審）アウト！
テンセブン　星野選手
Ten-seven, Hoshino!
He's coming.
（卓）こいつは くるぞ
Yes.
Good boy.
（オババ）いい子だ
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
I wish I at least got to spend my eternal exile in Europe...
Sweden or Germany or someplace.
First, I'll get into the top four and head to nationals.
Japan, huh?
You can do it, Kong!
（部員たち）頑張れ コンさーん！
Say hi to Kazama for me.
Huh?
ええい！
Got your ticket, Wenge?
Wenge, I'll be waiting for you.
（チャイナの母の
中国語）
Welcome home.
Match goes to Hoshino!
（主審）
マッチ トゥ 星野選手！
Kong Wenge is
Eliminated in the
Second Round
Kong Wenge is
Eliminated in the
Second Round
（子供のペコ）
ピンチの時には おいらを呼びな
Call me when you're in a pinch!
心の中で３回 唱えろ！
Chant this three times in your mind!
Enter the hero!
ヒーロー見参 ヒーロー見参
ヒーロー見参！
そうすりゃ
おいらが やってくる！
If you do that, I'll come to you!
ほーぅ！
ピンポン星から やってくる！
I'll come from Planet Ping Pong!
A red sun stares at me
The world goes blurry when I yawn
My wishes fluctuate like a metronome
Everything tells me this is the end
I do have some dreams, you know
Sometimes we breathe
and just seem to inhale the smoke of someone
somewhere out of sight
Then we are pure determination
I don't understand this wonderland
I won't get wet even if it rains
This is a wonderland
Once I've made it through this long tunnel
I'm sure that someone will kiss me